(Leonard:)You have no idea
how much you inconvenience
(Leonard:)the lives of everyone
around you.
It's exhausting!
(Sheldon:)You know what?
(Sheldon:)You think you're so tolerant,
(Sheldon:)but the truth is...
(Sheldon:)you're mean to me a lot.
(Sheldon:)Yeah,
you think
(Sheldon:)that I don't notice
all those sarcastic comments
(Sheldon:)and those eye rolls,
but I do. Hmm?
(Amy:)I have
excellent peripheral vision.
(Sheldon:)On a good day,
I can see my ears.
Sheldon, I-I'm sorry
if I hurt your feelings.
(Leonard:)I've been holding a lot
of this in for a while.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm sorry, too.
And if you want
(Sheldon:)to live with Penny,
then I think you should.
(Leonard:)Do you mean that?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Yeah, just put
on your squeaky shoes and...
(mimics squeaking)
your way out of my life.
(Leonard:)Come on, don't get upset.
(Sheldon:)I'm not upset.
(Sheldon:)I'm just imagining a world
without my best friend in it.